zealforlife.com 2019-03-30

# Website Terms of Use

Website Terms of Use
OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY                               D. Surveys and Promotions
Our Privacy Policy has been developed as an             Occasionally, you may voluntarily provide Personally
extension of our commitment to combine quality          Identifiable Information to complete surveys and
products and services with integrity in dealing with    questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We
users. The Policy is designed to assist you in the      use this information to improve our products and
understanding of how we collect, use and protect the    services and to ensure that we’re providing accurate
personal information provided to us.                    disclosures. We may also use your Personally
                                                        Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT                              and other marketing information that coincide with
When you visit our site, we collect two types of        your preferences.
information: personal information you actively choose
to disclose (“Active Information”) and information      You may customize your marketing preferences,
not visible to you that arises out of your browsing     or let us know if you do not wish to receive
of our site (“Passive Information”). Please note that   any promotional materials, by adjusting your
Passive Information is collected on an aggregate and    Subscriptions & Email options on the Site.
anonymous basis.
                                                        Active Information You Choose to Provide
1. Personally Identifiable Information                  In order to gain use of the site (become a “user”),
Personally Identifiable Information is information that we require you to disclose the following information:
identifies and is reasonably linked to you.             Name, Address and Phone Number.
A. Registration                                         We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to
When you register to become an authorized               protect the transmission of the information you
reseller of our products or services, we will collect   submit to us when you use our secure online forms.
Personally Identifiable Information (such as name,      The information you provide to us is stored securely.
address, email address, and telephone number).
This Personally Identifiable Information is securely    2. Passive Information
stored and may be accessed on our website. You          We store and collect various types of passive
are assigned an identification number and select        information on an aggregate and anonymous
your own password – both are needed to enter the        basis. This information may include such technical
Site and to access your Contact Information. Please     information as it pertains to your Internet protocol
safeguard your password in a secure location as         address, your device operating system and browser
we are not responsible for breaches into the system     type, cookies, and an address of a referring website
when access is willingly provided.                      or any other path you take to reach our website all
                                                        described in greater detail below.
B. Ordering
When you place an order for products or services,       Aggregate Information
we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such    This refers to information that does not, by itself,
as name, contact and billing information, credit card,  identify you as a specific individual. Such information
and other transactional information). We use this       would include the Uniform Resource Locator
information to deliver your order, process payment,     (“URL”) of the website that referred you to our Site,
and to communicate the status of your order.            your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (a number
                                                        automatically assigned to your computer whenever
C. Credit and Debit Card Storage                        you surf the web), your operating system and
Credit and debit card information collected at          browser type, and any search terms that you enter on
registration or for product orders is used only to      our Site. Our web server aggregates this information
process payment for the transaction and, generally,     in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site,
is not retained on our Site. However, you may           evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content
voluntarily elect to securely store multiple credit     or our Site in order to make your visit an easy and
cards to be used for product orders.                    enjoyable experience.

Website Terms of Use
We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote,       easier, faster and friendlier for users. Additionally,
report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate      cookies help us better understand the usage pattern
Information, provided that such information does        of the people that visit our site, which helps us
not personally identify you. We do not correlate any    improve our services. Passive Information may result
Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate  in your viewing of particular advertising based on
Information that we collect on our Site. If we do       your user habits.
correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will
be protected like any other Personally Identifiable     We reserve the right to use Active and Passive
Information under this Privacy Statement.               Information in order to prevent, detect and investigate
                                                        fraud, security breaches, or any other potentially
What is a Cookie?                                       prohibited or illegal activity.
Cookies are a feature of web browser software
that allows web servers to recognize the computer       We may use any Active Information or Passive
used to access a site. They are small pieces of data    Information provided to contact you about various
stored by a user’s browser to simplify subsequent       changes to our site, new services, features or
interactions with the site. This makes it easier for    products we offer. If at any time you do not wish to
a user to move from site to site and to complete        receive such information, you may “opt-out” of doing
transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make     so by adjusting your email settings in the back office
your online experience easier and more personalized.    of the website.
Our site utilizes cookies to collect information about  Your Information Relating to Hyperlinks
how our site is used. Passive Information gathered      You might be able to access other websites through
may include the date and time of visits, the site       our site via hyperlinks. When you do so, you are
pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited subjecting yourself to their privacy policies and data
just before and just after visiting our site. If you do collection. Please read the privacy policies of those
not wish to transmit “cookie” information about         sites to ensure you agree with the terms before using
yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your  such sites.
web browser.
                                                        Receiving and Sharing of Information from and
Our site’s servers also automatically identify your     with Third Parties
computer by its Internet Protocol address, which is     We reserve the right to receive information about you
a unique string of numbers that are assigned to your    from other third party sources, that help us update,
computer by your Internet Service Provider. The IP      expand and analyze our records and identify new
address may be used to address problems with our        customers. Furthermore, we may share Personal
server or to gather broad demographic information       Information necessary to the prevention of fraud,
about our users. We passively collect your IP Address.  illegal activities, and security breaches. Because of
                                                        this, it’s possible some of your personal information
HOW WE USE THE                                          may be shared with fraud prevention agencies. If
INFORMATION COLLECTED                                   false or inaccurate information is provided and fraud
Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly,           is identified, details of this fraud may be passed
or as contractors or agents at our direction, use       on to these agencies. Likewise, law enforcement
Active Information for purposes of administering our    and governmental agencies may access and use
core business functions, such as the fulfillment of     certain information pursuant to any law, regulation, or
orders or services, the furnishing of customer care     subpoena. This applies to information as it relates to
and support, and supplying the availability of other    both open and closed accounts.
products or services we think might be of interest
to our users.                                           Additionally, third parties who perform services
                                                        for us as it relates to security, payment, etc.
We use Passive Information to gather information        (such as Internet Service Providers, credit card
about our users and to enhance our site to make it      processors, and merchant banks) may also have

Website Terms of Use
access to your information in the performance of       Links to Other Websites
such necessary services.                               Links to third-party websites may be provided
                                                       solely for your information and convenience or to
Finally, we may disclose anonymous information         provide additional shopping for various other goods
about user habits to third party advertisers on our    and services through our Merchant and Services
site. Should we buy or sell assets of our company,     Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our
another company may need to review our company’s       Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the
assets, which might include your information, to       information practices of those websites nor do we
make business decisions as to whether to acquire       control their content or privacy policies. We suggest
such assets.                                           that you carefully review the privacy policies of each
                                                       site you visit.
HOW WE SECURE ACTIVE AND
PASSIVE INFORMATION                                    Children’s Privacy Protection
We secure your personal information submitted by       We take special care to protect the privacy needs
you by using reasonable efforts to prevent             of children and encourage parents to be an active
unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss  participant in their child’s online activities. Our site
of Active and Passive Information. Individual postings does not target and is not intended for children
on this site and other communications to our office    under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect
via email or standard mail may not be secure unless    Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we
we advise you that security measures are in place      discover personal data from a child through our site,
prior to your submission of information. Therefore, if we will eliminate that data. You may learn more about
you choose to communicate with us through these        protecting children’s privacy online by visiting:
means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and       www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-
we respectfully request that you do not send or post   your-childs-privacy-online.
sensitive information through these means.
                                                       Changes to This Policy
Accessing and Correcting Your Information              Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any         Policy will be posted on our Site and the date of
Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our  the newest version posted below. Please check
Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for  back frequently, especially before you submit any
its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise   Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see
correct Personally Identifiable Information provided   if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our
to us, you may edit your information online.           Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy
                                                       Statement in effect at the time of use.
Protecting Your Information
We acknowledge your trust and are committed            YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS
to take reasonable steps to protect Personally         THAT YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES
Identifiable Information provided from loss, misuse,   SET FORTH IN THIS POLICY. YOUR
and unauthorized access. We employ physical,           CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR
electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard      AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.
and secure your information. It is your responsibility
to safeguard the password you use to access our
Site and to promptly advise us if you ever suspect
that your password has been compromised. We
strongly encourage you to change your password
regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because
your identification number and password are specific
to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for
any and all use of our Site conducted with your
identification number and password.
                                                                                                         WTU_ENG_0618
